<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="settings_header_notice">Important Notice</string>
    <string name="settings_data_notice">Data Notice</string>
    <string name="settings_data_notice_details">Information regarding your data on NCBSinfo server.</string>
    <string name="settings_header_general">General Options</string>
    <string name="settings_header_transport">Transport related</string>
    <string name="settings_see_intro">See intro</string>
    <string name="settings_see_intro_details">What\'s new in this version?</string>
    <string name="settings_default_route">Default Transport</string>
    <string name="settings_default_transport_details">transport you want to see on Home.</string>
    <string name="settings_reset_transport">Reset Transport</string>
    <string name="settings_reset_transport_details">revert back to original transport routes.</string>
    <string name="settings_transport_last">Route Database</string>
    <string name="settings_transport_last_update">last update : 16 Oct 2017</string>
    <string name="settings_header_about">About us</string>
    <string name="settings_about">About NCBSinfo</string>
    <string name="settings_about_details">little bit about us!</string>
    <string name="settings_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="settings_feedback_details">Tell us what you think about this app.</string>
    <string name="settings_github">NCBSinfo on GitHub</string>
    <string name="settings_github_details">contribute to this open source project.</string>
    <string name="settings_app_details">NCBSinfo</string>
    <string name="settings_app_details_text">Current version: %1$d (%2$s)</string>
    <string name="settings_header_legal">Some legal stuff</string>
    <string name="settings_terms">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="settings_terms_details">nobody reads this!</string>
    <string name="settings_privacy">Privacy Statement</string>
    <string name="settings_privacy_details">what data we steal?</string>
    <string name="settings_notification">Notifications preference</string>
    <string name="settings_notification_details">occasional notifications: %s</string>
    <string name="settings_acknow">Acknowledgements and Credits</string>
    <string name="settings_acknow_details">standing on the shoulders of giants.</string>
    <string name="settings_default_route_name">%1$s - %2$s %3$s</string>
    <string name="settings_egg">Muggle Mode Dialogs</string>
    <string name="settings_remove_egg">Remove Dialogs</string>
    <string name="settings_remove_egg_details">I am not Muggle blooded.</string>
    <string name="settings_ron">Ron</string>
    <string name="settings_ron_details">Letter to Harry 1</string>
    <string name="settings_hermione">Hermione</string>
    <string name="settings_hermione_details">Letter to Harry 2</string>

    <string name="settings_reset_warning">This action will delete all existing transport route and will replace them with default routes. This action can not be undone. Are you sure you want to reset ?</string>


    <string name="about_us"><![CDATA[
 <b>NCBSinfo</b> is an application for regular use, especially helpful for people working at the National Centre for Biological Science (NCBS), Bangalore.
    Our aim is to create a mobile application, which will serve as an application-cum-database for important information pertaining to NCBS. With the help of this, we will try to reduce the time spent on searching for shuttle timings and contact numbers.
]]></string>

    <string name="terms"><![CDATA[ This is <b>NOT</b> an official NCBS app and has been created ONLY for personal use.
    All the information provided in this application was last updated on December 30, 2017.
    Though a lot of effort has been taken to curate the information,
    minor discrepancies may still exist. Developers are not responsible for any such information presented/conveyed
    through this application.
    In case of any bug/error(s), please report it to the developers; measures will be taken to rectify the same.]]></string>

    <string name="faq"><![CDATA[ &#8226; <b>Some of components of the UI look weird</b> <br> </br>
      This application is not yet designed for all screen sizes. Hence UI components might appear distorted or misplaced. <br> </br><br> </br>
      &#8226; <b>I am not being able to receive any event notifications</b> <br> </br>
      Please check if you have any task manager application that might be killing the NCBSinfo app. In that case, add this app to
      the white-list. <br> </br> <br> </br>
       &#8226; <b>There is no information in the event section</b> <br> </br>
       This can happen if there are no events retrieved from the server. The app will send request to data server
       depending on your network settings and will retrieve the data.
       If you want to manually sync the app, go to the developer\'s options and click on \"Sync Data now\".]]></string>

    <string name="privacy_statement">
        <![CDATA[
        Best part of an open source app is that you will know exactly what is going on inside the app. We encourage you to check
        our source code on GitHub (<a href="https://github.com/NCBSinfo/NCBSinfo"> https://github.com/NCBSinfo/NCBSinfo </a>). Code is heavily commented for readability.
        We ask for following permissions from you
        <br></br><br></br>
        <b>Permission <br></br> (and why?)</b> <br> </br> <br> </br>
        &#8226; <b> Internet Access </b> <br> </br> (To send anonymous crash report in case of crash) <br></br>
        &#8226; <b> Call Phone </b> <br> </br> (To directly call from this app) <br></br>
         <br> </br><br> </br>
        <b>Google and Firebase analytics</b><br> </br>
        We receive some anonymous statistics from all users who have installed this app.
        This information generally includes Android Version, Default language, Country, App version, Uninstall count etc.
        See <a href="https://policies.google.com/privacy">Google privacy policies</a> regarding this.
        <br> </br><br> </br>
        <b>Crash Report</b><br> </br>
        This will send us anonymous crash reports (if any) which we use to fix bugs and make the app better :)
        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>
        ]]>
</string>

    <string name="libraries_used">
        <![CDATA[
        We are very grateful to all the feedback and encouragement given by you. We would also like to
         acknowledge all the beta testers of this app. Special thanks to Pritha Ghosh for helping us out with grammar and spelling checks.
         All graphics inside the app was created by Rohit Suratekar. Icons were borrowed from Google Material Design as well as IBM design language resources.

        <br></br>We have used the following Open Source Android libraries while making this app and are very thankful to them.

        <br></br><br></br>
        &#8226; Design Library by Google <br></br>
        &#8226; Gson by Google <br></br>
        &#8226; Firebase by Google <br></br>
        &#8226; Butterknife by Jake Wharton <br></br>
        <br></br><br></br>
        See our <a href="https://github.com/NCBSinfo/NCBSinfo"> source code </a> for detailed library information.

]]>
</string>

    <string name="notice">
        <![CDATA[ In continuation with our <a href="https://github.com/NCBSinfo/NCBSinfo/releases/tag/v6.0">previous</a>
        announcement regarding halting further development,
        we will be generating long term support (LTS) version of current app.
        For this purpose, we will be removing all cloud related functions.
        Now all app functions will be offline. Authentication steps will be discarded i.e. you can no
        longer create account or login to your existing account.
        All user data will be deleted in future.
        If you want to access any of your past data related to synced routes,
        please contact <a href="mailto:contact@secretbiology.com">contact@secretbiology.com</a>. All user data and backups will be kept till <b>1 Feb 2019</b>.

]]>
</string>
</resources>