<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="settings_app_version">6.5.8</string>
    <string name="settings_header_notice">Important Information</string>
    <string name="settings_development_notice">Announcement</string>
    <string name="settings_development_notice_details">Information regarding future app development.
    </string>
    <string name="settings_header_general">General Options</string>
    <string name="settings_header_transport">Transport related</string>
    <string name="settings_default_route">Default Transport</string>
    <string name="settings_route_name">%1$s - %2$s (%3$s)</string>
    <string name="settings_default_transport_details">transport you want to see on Home.</string>
    <string name="settings_default_transport_dialog">Please select a route from the following list. This route
        will be shown on your home screen.
    </string>
    <string name="settings_reset_transport">Reset Transport</string>
    <string name="settings_reset_transport_details">revert back to original transport routes.</string>
    <string name="settings_transport_last">Route Database</string>
    <string name="settings_transport_last_update">last update : %s</string>
    <string name="settings_header_about">About us</string>
    <string name="settings_about">About NCBSinfo</string>
    <string name="settings_about_details">little bit about us!</string>
    <string name="settings_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="settings_feedback_details">Tell us what you think about this app.</string>
    <string name="settings_github">NCBSinfo on GitHub</string>
    <string name="settings_github_details">contribute to this open source project.</string>
    <string name="settings_app_details">NCBSinfo</string>
    <string name="settings_app_details_text">Current version: %1$d (%2$s)</string>
    <string name="settings_header_legal">Some legal stuff</string>
    <string name="settings_terms">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="settings_terms_details">nobody reads this!</string>
    <string name="settings_privacy">Privacy Statement</string>
    <string name="settings_privacy_details">what data we steal?</string>
    <string name="settings_acknow">Acknowledgements and Credits</string>
    <string name="settings_acknow_details">standing on the shoulders of giants.</string>
    <string name="settings_default_route_name">%1$s - %2$s %3$s</string>
    <string name="settings_crash_report">Anonymous Crash Reporting</string>
    <string name="settings_crash_report_details">Currently reporting is : %s</string>


    <string name="settings_reset_warning">This action will delete all existing transport route and will replace them
        with default routes. This action can not be undone. Are you sure you want to reset?
    </string>


    <string name="about_us"><![CDATA[
 <b>NCBSinfo</b> is an application for regular use, especially helpful for people working at the National Centre for Biological Science (NCBS), Bangalore.
    Our aim is to create a mobile application, which will serve as an application-cum-database for important information pertaining to NCBS. With the help of this, we will try to reduce the time spent on searching for shuttle timings and contact numbers.
]]></string>

    <string name="terms"><![CDATA[ This is <b>NOT</b> an official NCBS app and has been created ONLY for personal use.
    All the information provided in this application was last updated on January 1, 2019.
    Though a lot of effort has been taken to curate the information,
    minor discrepancies may still exist. Developers are not responsible for any such information presented/conveyed
    through this application.
    In case of any bug/error(s), please report it to the developers; measures will be taken to rectify the same.

        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>]]></string>

    <string name="privacy_statement">
        <![CDATA[
        Best part of an open source app is that you will know exactly what is going on inside the app. We encourage you to check
        our source code on GitHub (<a href="https://github.com/NCBSinfo/NCBSinfo"> https://github.com/NCBSinfo/NCBSinfo </a>). Code is heavily commented for readability.
        We ask for following permissions from you
        <br></br><br></br>
        <b>Permission <br></br> (and why?)</b> <br> </br> <br> </br>
        &#8226; <b> Internet Access </b> <br> </br> (To send anonymous crash report in case of crash) <br></br>
        &#8226; <b> Call Phone </b> <br> </br> (To directly call from this app) <br></br>
         <br> </br><br> </br>
         However, this app will work perfectly fine without any of above permissions. You can block them if you
         are really paranoid about them :) <br> </br><br> </br>
        <b>Google and Firebase analytics</b><br> </br>
        We receive some anonymous statistics from all users who have installed this app.
        This information generally includes Android Version, Default language, Country, App version, Uninstall count etc.
        See <a href="https://policies.google.com/privacy">Google privacy policies</a> regarding this.
        <br> </br><br> </br>
        <b>Crash Report</b><br> </br>
        This will send us anonymous crash reports (if any) which we use to fix bugs and make the app better :) However,
        if you have switched OFF this from settings, this report will NOT be sent.
        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>
        Check latest and full privacy statement <a href="https://github.com/NCBSinfo/NCBSinfo/blob/master/PrivacyPolicy.md"> here </a>.
        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="libraries_used">
        <![CDATA[
        We are very grateful to all the feedback and encouragement given by you. We would also like to
         acknowledge all the beta testers of this app. Special thanks to Pritha Ghosh for helping us out with grammar and spelling checks.
         All graphics inside the app were created by Rohit Suratekar. Icons were borrowed from Google Material Design as well as IBM design language resources.

        <br></br>We have used the following Open Source Android libraries while making this app and are very thankful to them.

        <br></br><br></br>
        &#8226; AndroidX Libraries by Google <br></br>
        &#8226; Architecture Components by Google <br></br>
        &#8226; Dagger2 by Google <br></br>
        <br></br><br></br>
        See our <a href="https://github.com/NCBSinfo/NCBSinfo"> source code </a> for detailed library information.
        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>

]]>
    </string>


    <string name="halted_development">
        <![CDATA[
       Dear app user, <br> </br><br> </br>
        The NCBSinfo project started as a small personal app in December 2016, which I had used to track shuttle timings in NCBS.
        Soon it\'s user base expanded and now (as of December 2018) it has almost 450 daily users and more than 1000 installs.
        Unfortunately, now I can not dedicate more time for maintaining this app and have to stop further development. However,
        to make this self-sustained, I have added a solid foundation for editing and managing one\'s own timetable. If you
        are not aware of this function, please check \'Manage Transport\' option from \'Information\' section. You will be able to
        use this app smoothly, even if there are any changes in transport timings. One can even create their own routes.
        I will fix (any) bugs and timetable changes until 16 October 2019. If anyone is interested in developing
        this app further, feel free to contribute to this open source app on <a href="https://github.com/NCBSinfo/NCBSinfo"> GitHub</a>.
        If you have any suggestion or feedback, please drop me an email on <a href="mailto:contact@secretbiology.com">contact@secretbiology.com</a> or
        <a href="mailto:ncbs.mod@gmail.com">ncbs.mod@gmail.com</a>. <br> </br> <br> </br> I am very
        grateful for all the love and encouragement provided by you. I hope this app will also help you in the future.
        Thank you!<br> </br> Bidding Adieu!!
        <br> </br><br> </br>
        Yours<br> </br>
        <a href="http://rohitsuratekar.com/">Rohit Suratekar</a>
        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>
        <br> </br>
]]>
    </string>

    <string name="bid_adieu">Bid Adieu</string>
</resources>