<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

     <string name="egg_ron">
Look, I\' really sorry about that telephone call. I hope the Muggles
didn\'t give you a hard time. I asked Dad, and he reckons I shouldn\'t
have shouted.\n
It\'s amazing here in Egypt. Bill\'s taken us around all the tombs and you
wouldn\'t believe the curses those old Egyptian wizards put on them. Mum
wouldn\'t let Ginny come in the last one. There were all these mutant
skeletons in there, of Muggles who\'d broken in and grown extra heads and
stuff.\n
I couldn\'t believe it when Dad won the Daily Prophet Draw. Seven hundred
galleons! Most of it\'s gone on this trip, but they\'re going to buy me a
new wand for next year.\n
Harry remembered only too well the occasion when Ron\'s old wand had
snapped. It had happened when the car the two of them had been flying to
Hogwarts had crashed into a tree on the school grounds.\n
We\'ll be back about a week before term starts and we\'ll be going up to
London to get my wand and our new books. Any chance of meeting you
there?\n
Don\'t let the Muggles get you down!\n
Try and come to London
    </string>

    <string name="egg_hermione">
        Ron wrote to me and told me about his phone call to your Uncle Vernon. I
do hope you\'re all right.\n
I\'m on holiday in France at the moment and I didn\'t know how I was going
to send this to you — what if they\'d opened it at customs? — but then
Hedwig turned up! I think she wanted to make sure you got something for
your birthday for a change. I bought your present by owl-order; there
was an advertisement in the Daily Prophet (I\'ve been getting it
delivered; it\'s so good to keep up with what\'s going on in the wizarding
world), Did you see that picture of Ron and his family a week ago? I bet
he\'s learning loads. I\'m really jealous — the ancient Egyptian wizards
were fascinating.\n
There\'s some interesting local history of witchcraft here, too. I\'ve
rewritten my whole History of Magic essay to include some of the things
I\'ve found out, I hope it\'s not too long — it\'s two rolls of parchment
more than Professor Binns asked for.\n
Ron says he\'s going to be in London in the last week of the holidays.
Can you make it? Will your aunt and uncle let you come? I really hope
you can. If not, I\'ll see you on the Hogwarts Express on September
first!
</string>
</resources>