<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="settings_general">General</string>
    <string name="settings_change_mode">Change Mode</string>
    <string name="settings_change_mode_summary">Change between online and offline modes.</string>
    <string name="settings_about_ncbinfo">About NCBSinfo</string>
    <string name="settings_delete_preference">Clear preferences</string>
    <string name="settings_delete_preference_summary">Delete all of your preferences and customizations</string>
    <string name="settings_faq">Frequently Asked Questions</string>
    <string name="settings_faq_summary">Known problems faced while using different features of this app</string>
    <string name="settings_about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="settings_about_us_summary">Little bit about us</string>
    <string name="settings_contribute">Contribute to NCBSinfo</string>
    <string name="settings_contribute_summary">Fork us on GitHub and join open source app making</string>
    <string name="settings_terms">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="settings_privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="settings_privacy_summary">What information we collect and why</string>
    <string name="settings_terms_summary">Nobody reads this anyways!</string>
    <string name="settings_default_view">Default transport</string>
    <string name="settings_default_view_summary">This transport will be shown first when you open the app</string>
    <string name="settings_hurryup">It\'s almost time (in min)</string>
    <string name="settings_hurryup_summary">The color will turn red if the next transport is within this time period</string>


    <string name="about_us"><![CDATA[ <b>NCBSinfo</b> is an application for regular use, specially helpful for people working at the National Centre for Biological Science (NCBS), Bangalore.
    Our aim is to create a mobile application which will serve as an application-cum-database for important things pertaining to NCBS. With the help of this, we will try to reduce the time spent on searching useful information like shuttle timings and contact numbers.]]></string>

    <string name="terms"><![CDATA[ This is <b>NOT</b> an official NCBS app and has been created ONLY for personal use.
    All the information (except event updates) provided in this application was last updated on 21 June 2016.
    Though a lot of effort has been taken to curate the information,
    minor discrepancies may still exist. Developers are not responsible for any such information presented/conveyed
    through this application.
    In case of any bug/error(s), please report it to the developers; measures will be taken to rectify the same. ]]></string>

    <string name="faq"><![CDATA[ &#8226; <b>Some of components of the UI look weird</b> <br> </br>
      This application is not yet designed for all screen sizes. Hence UI components might appear distorted or misplaced. <br> </br><br> </br>
      &#8226; <b>I am not being able to receive any notifications from events</b> <br> </br>
      Please check if you have any task manager application which is killing the NCBSinfo app. In that case, add this app into
      the white-list. <br> </br> <br> </br>
       &#8226; <b>There is nothing in the event section</b> <br> </br>
       This can happen if there are no events retrieved from the server. App will make request to data server
       depending on your network settings and will retrieve the data.
       If you want to manually sync your app, go to developer\'s options and click on \"Sync Data now\".]]></string>

    <string name="privacy_statement">
        <![CDATA[

        Best part of open source app is that you will know exactly what is going on inside app. We encourage you to check
        our source code on GitHub (https://github.com/NCBSinfo/NCBSinfo). Code is heavily commented for readability. We collect
        various personal and general information from this app to make better user experience. Following is the list of all
        information we get from users. <br></br><br></br>

        <b>What information we collect (and why?)</b> <br> </br> <br> </br>
        &#8226; <b> Name and email </b> <br> </br> (To authenticate you on our server) <br></br>
        &#8226; <b> Default route </b> <br> </br> (To customize your app when you login again) <br></br>
        &#8226; <b> Unique Token </b> <br> </br> (This token is generated by Firebase service through which you can get notifications from admins)<br></br>
        &#8226; <b> Current NCBSinfo App version </b> <br> </br> (To remind you about new updates which will be free of bugs and issues) <br></br>
        &#8226; <b> Last login </b> <br> </br> (To design network sync algorithms.) <br></br>
        &#8226; <b> App open count </b> <br> </br> (To check active users.) <br></br>
        &#8226; <b> Number of network calls done by app</b> <br> </br> (To block spammers and malicious app modifications ) <br></br>
        <br> </br><br> </br>

        If you don\'t want any of above information to be send to our server, you can use OFFLINE mode. <br></br>
        <b>WE DO NOT COLLECT ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM OFFLINE MODE USERS.</b><br></br><br></br>

        <b>Google and Firebase analytics</b><br> </br>
        Besides above personal information, we also receive some anonymous statistics of all users who have installed this app.
        This information generally includes Android Version, Default language, Country, App version, Uninstall count etc.

        <br> </br><br> </br>
        <b>Crash Report</b><br> </br>
        This will send us anonymous crash reports (if any) which we use to fix bugs and make app better :)
        ]]>

    </string>

</resources>